Hi everyone! We are Huanong Brothers.
Our...I mean,
our bamboo rats shred is already full,
and we have no more cells now.
We now have rented one more site.
to make the bamboo rats....to keep slightly more.
It's just behind us. Let me take you to have a look.
This whole area is ours, and this side too.
These will be removed in a few days.
These are....sand and rocks.
And here as well.
Here is a lot or reed.
Above it is a pond.
I wonder if there're any fish.
I'll come with my draining machine to drain away the water next time.
Look! Spring water is flowing down from there too.
It seems that the spring water is a very big water.
It's flowing down right from the peak.
Look! Here is also an,
an ant lair.
Ayo! You need to move away now!
I'm...
smashing their lair and then they'll build a new one somewhere else.
A lot of ants.
Well, I'll leave them alone.
They'll move away on their own.
Look! These were just built a couple of days ago.
Um, the cells that we are not building,
are not the shaky one like those we are now having.
These are all leveled.
Look! The line is still here.
It can be made very straight using this, by pulling a line from here.
Then we can build slowly as there is no hurry.
Very pretty cells can be built!
These are breeding cells, all these here are breeding cells.
Those are merchandise, for merchandise rats.
Let's take a look at other places.
Some cells are being built here too.
This side, from, from here, all the way, it should be around 800 meter square.
Together with 800 up stair, it means 1600, 1600 meter square.
This empty space is more than 1700 meter square, which is almost 3 "mu", 3 "mu" of land. (1 "mu" = 666.666 meter square)
Then the reed, we can just fix, fix that area
and plant some elephant grass,
some elephant grass, then it would be nice.
Um. Let me go up stair to have a look.
There is still, very large, it's very large, up stair.
Look! This is a residential area. It's divided into units.
Let me have a look there. It's a bit dark.
I need a key.
Wa! Here is suite.
Here, with the flowery pattern, whose' that?
Wa! This is wonderful!
Next time when I have the time, I'll have a feast of you.
Wasps. A big lair.
Wa! It seems that there are...pupa.
I'll eat them next time.
Here, this is a couple of,
jars, jars for pickling vegetables.
We can have, have pickles.
Wa! A lot of rooms.
This one, this one
This is an office.
Wa! There are even two chairs.
They are new, just a bit dirty. Should be fine after some cleaning.
There is even a bed.
The glass is a bit broken.
Wa! This is
Why is here a string?
Here is a string.
Has somebody slept here?
Slept on a piece of string.
Don't fall.
It would be nice if there were wires for up there. Then I could swing.
when I have nothing to do.
This can be taken to, to, to knock the chestnuts, I mean this rod.
It's very dry, and light.
I can hold it by just one hand.
Let me bring it back.
to knock the chestnuts at Mr. Cameraman's place.
It's very firm.
Both of them.
Ey! It's elastic.
Um?
Whose duck is it?
Wa! Here are two little ponds too.
I can keep some fish too.
Keep some fish.
Put some snakehead fish.
The edge needs to be covered. Otherwise, it would be as hot as making a soup,
and the fish would be boiled to death.
Look? Down there are three ponds.
What's that? I just saw something moving.
Let me throw a rock.
No response.
I'll catch it after draining out the water next time.
There is another big pond.
Eh, I had a look a couple of days ago.
there're a lot of fish.
Next time when we have the time, we can go fishing there.
Look! No rod, you don't even need a rod.
Above the pond is already a lot of bamboo.
We can chop some bamboo, and fish right there.
Now a road, a road is being paved over there.
So the water is quite, quite dirty.
But it will become very clean tomorrow.
This river,
is pretty.
Look! A road is being paved in our village.
From here, all the way...
From the national highway, up there is the national highway, the road is paved, paved all the way to our village.
This will be paved by tarmacadam
with two lanes.
Then all types of cars can come to our village.
I should be 6 meters, 6 meters width
with two lanes.
I think next month, it should be completed by next month.
Now the watering car is over there.
The paving machines are over there.
It should be completed right away.
Alright! The video ends here.
We need to go back to feed the bamboo rats.